/*global angular */

angular.module('mathSkills').value('data3_1', {
    title: '3.1 Multiply Whole Numbers',
    path: '3.1-multiply-whole-numbers',
    children: [{
        title: 'Multiply Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Find the product of the whole numbers:}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\multiplywholes{math}{partial}{839}{3}}}',
                answer: '\\input{2517}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\multiplywholes{math}{complete}{839}{3}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Multiply Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Find the product of the whole numbers:}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\multiplywholes{math}{partial}{596}{6}}}',
                answer: '\\input{3576}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\multiplywholes{math}{complete}{596}{6}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Multiply Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Find the product of the whole numbers:}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\multiplywholes{english}{partial}{6453}{4}}}',
                answer: '\\input{25812}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\multiplywholes{math}{complete}{6453}{4}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Multiply Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Find the product of the whole numbers:}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\multiplywholes{math}{partial}{4049}{7}}}',
                answer: '\\input{28343}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\multiplywholes{math}{complete}{4049}{7}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Multiply Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Find the product of the whole numbers:}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\multiplywholes{math}{partial}{97}{74}}}',
                answer: '\\input{7178}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\multiplywholes{math}{complete}{97}{74}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Multiply Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Find the product of the whole numbers:}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\multiplywholes{english}{partial}{34}{29}}}',
                answer: '\\input{986}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\multiplywholes{math}{complete}{34}{29}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Multiply Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Find the product of the whole numbers:}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\multiplywholes{math}{partial}{645}{90}}}',
                answer: '\\input{58050}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\multiplywholes{math}{complete}{645}{90}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Multiply Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Find the product of the whole numbers:}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\multiplywholes{math}{partial}{374}{29}}}',
                answer: '\\input{10846}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\multiplywholes{math}{complete}{374}{29}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Multiply Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Find the product of the whole numbers:}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\multiplywholes{english}{partial}{300}{356}}}',
                answer: '\\input{106800}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\multiplywholes{math}{complete}{300}{356}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Multiply Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Find the product of the whole numbers:}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\multiplywholes{math}{partial}{508}{602}}}',
                answer: '\\input{305}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\multiplywholes{math}{complete}{508}{602}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }]
});
